Boston Streets Collection MS102
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Boston City Directories, 1845 -- 1925; 1845 -- 1960; MS102.002; 2703 Digital Object(s)
  - 1870, MS102.002.006; 527 Digital Object(s)
    - Index to Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00484; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Business Directory of out of Town Advertisers, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00485; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Business Directory of out of Town Advertisers from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Business Directory of out of Town Advertisers, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00486; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00487; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Street Directory from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00488; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00489; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00490; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00491; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00492; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00493; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00494; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00495; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00496; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00497; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00498; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00499; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00500; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00501; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00502; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00503; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00504; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00505; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00506; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00507; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00508; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00509; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00510; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00511; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Street Directory; Blocks, Buildings, &c., 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00512; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Street Directory; Blocks, Buildings, &c. from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Wharves, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00513; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Wharves from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Ward Boundaries, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00514; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Ward Boundaries from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Ward Boundaries, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00515; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Halls, Cemetaries, Etc., 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00516; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Halls, Cemetaries, Etc. from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Post Office, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00517; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Post Office from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Militia, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00518; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Militia from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Boston Directory of 1870, MS102.002.006.DO.00519; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Removals, additions and corrections page 5; pages 50-99 of the city directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Boston Directory of 1870, MS102.002.006.DO.00520; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Pages 100-199 of the city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Boston Directory of 1870, MS102.002.006.DO.00521; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      pages 200-299 of the city directory Institue of Museum and Library Services
    - Boston Directory of 1870, MS102.002.006.DO.00522; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      pages 300-399 of the city directory Institue of Museum and Library Services
    - Boston Directory of 1870, MS102.002.006.DO.00523; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      pages 400-499 of the city directory Institue of Museum and Library Services
    - Boston Directory of 1870, MS102.002.006.DO.00524; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      pages 500-599 of the city directory Institue of Museum and Library Services
    - Boston Directory of 1870, MS102.002.006.DO.00525; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      pages 600-699 of the city directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Boston Directory of 1870, MS102.002.006.DO.00526; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      pages 700-720/36 of the city directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Boston Directory of 1870, MS102.002.006.DO.00527; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Text version of scanned multipage tiffs of the city directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
  - 1872, MS102.002.007; 552 Digital Object(s)
    This sub-series contains the Boston directory for 1872.
    - Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00001; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Advertisements from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00002; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Steam & Gas Pipe Works., 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00003; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Boston Steam & Gas Pipe Works. from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Howard Watch and Clock Co., 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00004; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Howard Watch and Clock Co. from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00005; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00006; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00007; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00008; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00009; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Contents, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00010; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Contents from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Counting-House Almanac, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00011; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Counting-House Almanac from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Index to Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00012; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Index to Advertisements from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Index to Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00013; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Index to Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00014; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Index to Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00015; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Index to Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00016; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Index to Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00017; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Index to Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00018; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Index to Advertisements, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00019; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Business Directory of Out of Town Advertisers, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00020; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Business Directory of Out of Town Advertisers from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Business Directory of Out of Town Advertisers, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00021; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Business Directory of Out of Town Advertisers, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00022; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Newspapers, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00023; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Newspapers from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Newspapers, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00024; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Newspapers, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00025; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Bronner's, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00026; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Bronner's from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Newspapers, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00027; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Bickford, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00028; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Bickford from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00029; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Street Directory from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00030; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00031; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00032; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00033; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00034; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00035; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00036; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00037; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00038; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00039; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00040; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00041; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00042; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00043; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00044; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00045; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00046; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00047; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00048; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00049; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00050; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00051; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00052; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00053; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00054; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00055; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Street Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00056; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Ward Boundaries, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00057; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Ward Boundaries from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Halls and Blocks, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00058; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Halls and Blocks from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Fireman's Fund Ins. Co., 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00059; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Fireman's Fund Ins. Co. from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Boston Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00060; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Boston Directory from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Alfred Mudge & Son, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00061; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Alfred Mudge & Son from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Alfred Mudge & Son, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00062; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00063; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Boston Business Directory from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00064; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00065; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00066; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00067; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00068; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00069; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00070; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00071; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00072; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00073; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00074; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00075; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00076; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00077; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00078; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00079; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00080; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00081; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00082; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00083; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00084; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00085; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00086; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00087; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00088; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00089; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00090; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00091; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00092; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00093; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00094; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00095; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00096; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00097; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00098; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00099; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00100; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00101; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00102; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00103; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00104; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00105; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00106; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00107; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00108; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00109; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00110; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00111; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00112; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00113; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00114; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00115; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00116; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00117; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00118; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00119; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00120; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00121; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00122; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00123; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00124; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00125; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00126; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00127; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00128; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00129; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00130; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00131; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00132; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00133; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00134; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00135; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00136; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00137; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00138; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00139; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00140; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00141; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00142; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00143; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00144; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00145; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00146; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00147; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00148; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00149; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00150; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00151; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00152; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00153; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00154; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00155; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00156; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00157; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00158; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00159; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00160; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00161; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00162; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00163; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00164; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00165; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00166; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00167; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00168; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00169; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Boston Business Directory, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00170; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Illustration, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00171; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Illustration from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - J.H. Bufford's, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00172; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of J.H. Bufford's from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Expresses Running from Boston, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00173; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Expresses Running from Boston from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Expresses, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00174; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
      Page image of Expresses from the 1872 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Expresses, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00175; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Expresses, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00176; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Expresses, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00177; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Expresses, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00178; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Expresses, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00179; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Expresses, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00180; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Expresses, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00181; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Expresses, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00182; Sampson, Davenport and Co.
    - Expresses, 1872; MS102.002.007.DO.00183; Sampson, Davenport and Co.